EUNAH KIM

Kissimmee, FL 34743

407-675-0415 | Eunahkim92@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/eunahjkim/ · Portfolio: eunahk92.github.io/React-Portfolio/

Github: github.com/eunahk92

Ambitious Full Stack Web Developer with over 8 years of experience in a leadership role in the Food & Beverage industry. Recent recipient of a certificate from the University of Central Florida Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp that allowed me to acquire and hone my skills. Professional strengths include multitasking, communication and time management with solid ability to learn quickly and stay calm under high pressure and fast-paced environments, collaborate with a team or work independently, and a strong focus on attention to detail. Passionate to make an impact in creating intuitive applications and continue my growth in this ever-growing field.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Node.Js., Express, JavaScript, jQuery, React.js, React, JSX, GIT, GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, Sequelize. Mongoose, Handlebars, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Materialize, APIs, Heroku, Terminal, AJAX, Restful API, ES6, React Hooks, JSON

PROJECTS

TRAVELERS COMPASS

GITHUB REPO: HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/KIMNANA45/THE-TRAVELERS-COMPASS DEPLOYED PROJECT: HTTPS://GENTLE-RIDGE-35373.HEROKUAPP.COM/

<u>Role</u>: Used Axios to make requests to server-side APIs and create responsive web pages. Using React components styled with Bootstrap CSS Framework, we leveraged mongoose database to implement numerous functionalities of the application.

<u>Utilized</u>: HTML, CSS, JSON, Express, Axios, Moment.js, Filestack React, Algolia-Places package, Server-side APIs, React, Mongoose

MOTHER TRUCKERS

GITHUB REPO: HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/EUNAHK92/MOTHER-TRUCKERS DEPLOYED PROJECT: HTTPS://ARCANE-WATERS-56136.HEROKUAPP.COM/

Role: Used jQuery AJAX method to make requests to Mapquest API. Using Express-Handlebars, created HTML pages that allowed users to create user accounts and post/ find nearby Food Trucks utilizing Sequelize to retain data.

<u>Utilized</u>: HTML, CSS, Express, Express-Handlebars, Sequelize, Node, Socket.io, Passport library, AJAX, CRUD application

EMPLOYEE-SYSTEM-DB

GITHUB REPO: HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/EUNAHK92/EMPLOYEE-SYS

Role: A CMS interface to build a command-line application for managing a company's employees.

Utilized: Javascript, Node, Inquirer library, mySQL, Async Await

EXPERIENCE

OCTOBER 2020 – CURRENT | ORLANDO, FL ASSOCIATE SOFTWARE TESTER, VERATA HEALTH

- Executing manual test cases and analyzing results.
- Defining and maintaining testing activities while documenting testing phases and defects.
- Report bugs and errors to development team.

OCTOBER 2020 – CURRENT | ORLANDO, FL TUTOR AND CENTRAL GRADER, 2U

- Support students enrolled in University Bootcamps globally through 1:1 sessions covering Full-Stack Web Development technical skills, such as front-end programming languages and frameworks, databases, server-side languages and libraries, version control (Git and Github), and deployment servers (Heroku).
- Provide assignment grades and feedback in a detailed, clear, and supportive way of learning in Full-Stack Web Development topics.

MARCH 2019 – APRIL 2020 | ORLANDO, FL RESTAURANT ASST. MANAGER, FOUR SEASONS RESORT ORLANDO

- Continued to develop a strong team of employees that delivered a high level of exceptional guest service, reflected and mentioned in Medallia scores (post-stay surveys) and management and employee surveys.
- Developed strong attention to details with the ability to manage and multitask, while demonstrating exceptional skills and maintaining luxury standards.

EDUCATION

SEPTEMBER 2020 | ORLANDO, FL

BOOTCAMP CERTIFICATE, UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL FLORIDA

A 24-week intensive Full-Stack Web Development program that develops the programming skills in HTML5, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap Framework, Node JS, MySQL/ Sequelize, MongoDB/ Mongoose, Express, Handlebars.JS, and React.JS while encouraging collaboration with other developers to create intuitive web applications.

DECEMBER 2015 | ORLANDO, FL

BS EVENT AND HOSPITALITY MANAGEMENT, UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL FLORIDA

Member of Rho Lambda: National Sorority Leadership Recognition Society

Delta Phi Lambda Sorority, Inc: Finance Lead for Southeast Formal 2015, Treasurer 2014-2015, Public Relations Chair 2014-2015, Diversified Greek Council Liaison 2013, Co-Events Coordinator 2013 & 2015.